Register of the Gerald Lee Warren papers, 1956-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- White House Subject File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 90-217)
  - Foreign policy
    - Japan
      - Messages
        - 1969 November (Box-folder 168: 19)
        - 1972 March (Box-folder 168: 20)
        - 1973 January (Box-folder 168: 21)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 168: 22)
        - 1975 July (Box-folder 168: 23)
      - Newsletters, 1973 July (Box-folder 168: 24)
      - Pool reports, 1974
        - May (Box-folder 168: 25)
        - August (Box-folder 168: 26)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 168: 27)
          Photocopy.
        - 1969 November (Box-folder 168: 28)
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 168: 29)
        - 1973 November (Box-folder 168: 30)
        - 1974 April (Box-folder 168: 31)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 168: 32)
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 168: 33)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 168: 34)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 168: 35)
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 168: 36)
        - 1971 September-October (Box-folder 168: 37-38)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 168: 39)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 168: 40)
      - Remarks, 1973 July (Box-folder 168: 41)
      - Statements
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 168: 42)
        - 1972 May (Box-folder 168: 43)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 168: 44)
      - Telegrams, 1969 December (Box-folder 168: 45)
    - Kenya
      - Memoranda, 1973 October (Box-folder 168: 46)
      - News summaries, 1973 September (Box-folder 168: 47)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 168: 48)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 168: 49)
    - Korea
      - Interviews (printed copy), 1975 June (Box-folder 168: 50)
      - Meetings, 1975 May (Box-folder 168: 51)
      - Newsletters
        - 1975 June-July (Box-folder 168: 52-53)
        - 1975-1976 (Box-folder 168: 54)
      - Press briefings, 1975 July (Box-folder 168: 55)
      - Press conferences, 1969 April (Box-folder 168: 56)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 168: 57)
        - 1970 July (Box-folder 168: 58)
      - Printed matter, 1974 November (Box-folder 168: 59)
      - Remarks, 1975 June (Box-folder 168: 60)
      - Statements, 1975 June (Box-folder 168: 61)
      - Telegrams (photocopy), undated (Box-folder 168: 62)
    - Laos
      - Fact sheets, undated (Box-folder 168: 63)
      - Interviews
        - Undated (Box-folder 168: 64)
        - 1971 February (Box-folder 168: 65)
      - Meetings, 1972 October (Box-folder 168: 66)
      - Memoranda, undated (Box-folder 168: 67)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 168: 68)
      - Newsletters
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 168: 69)
        - General, 1971 (Box-folder 168: 70)
      - News summaries, 1971
        - February (Box-folder 168: 71)
        - April (Box-folder 168: 72)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 168: 73)
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 168: 74)
        - 1975
          - May (Box-folder 168: 75)
          - July (Box-folder 168: 76)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 169: 1)
        - 1970
          - January (Box-folder 169: 2)
          - March (Box-folder 169: 3)
      - Printed matter, undated (Box-folder 169: 4)
      - Remarks, 1970 March (Box-folder 169: 5)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 169: 6)
        - 1971 February (Box-folder 169: 7)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 169: 8)
      - Telegrams, 1973 February (Box-folder 169: 9)
      - Television news reports
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 169: 10)
        - 1971 February (Box-folder 169: 11)
      - Wire releases, undated (Box-folder 169: 12)
    - Latin America
      - Communiques, 1974 April (Box-folder 169: 13)
      - Correspondence, 1970 February (Box-folder 169: 14)
      - Fact sheets, undated (Box-folder 169: 15)
      - Meetings, 1971 October (Box-folder 169: 16)
      - Messages
        - Undated (Box-folder 169: 17)
        - 1970 February (Box-folder 169: 18)
      - News summaries, 1971 November (Box-folder 169: 19)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 169: 20)
        - 1969 October (Box-folder 169: 21)
        - 1972 April (Box-folder 169: 22)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 169: 23)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 169: 24)
        - 1969 February-March (Box-folder 169: 25-26)
        - 1971 November (Box-folder 169: 27)
      - Press kits (Box-folder 169: 28)
      - Press releases
        - 1971 October-November (Box-folder 169: 29-30)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 169: 31)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 April (Box-folder 169: 32)
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 169: 33)
      - Remarks
        - 1970 July (Box-folder 169: 34)
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 169: 35)
        - 1972 April (Box-folder 169: 36)
        - 1974 April (Box-folder 169: 37)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 169: 38)
      - Schedules, undated (Box-folder 169: 39)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 169: 40)
        - 1969 February (Box-folder 169: 41)
        - 1971 August (Box-folder 169: 42)
        - 1972 April (Box-folder 169: 43)
      - Telegrams
        - 1969 November (Box-folder 169: 44)
        - 1971 October (Box-folder 169: 45)
    - Liberia
      - Correspondence, undated (Box-folder 169: 46)
      - Meetings, undated (Box-folder 169: 47)
      - Memoranda, 1971 December (Box-folder 169: 48)
      - Press briefings, undated (Box-folder 169: 49)
      - Press conferences, 1971 November (Box-folder 169: 50)
      - Remarks
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 169: 51)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 169: 52)
    - Libya
      - Communiques, 1969 December (Box-folder 169: 53)
      - Press briefings
        - 1969 October (Box-folder 169: 54)
        - 1970 March (Box-folder 169: 55)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 169: 56)
    - Malaysia, meetings, 1969 October (Box-folder 169: 57)
    - Malta
      - Press briefings, 1971 August (Box-folder 169: 58)
      - Statements, 1971 December (Box-folder 169: 59)
    - Mexico
      - Correspondence, undated (Box-folder 169: 60)
      - Meetings, 1974 June (Box-folder 169: 61)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 169: 62)
        - 1970 August (Box-folder 169: 63)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974 December (Box-folder 169: 64)
      - Press briefings, 1970 June (Box-folder 169: 65)
      - Press conferences, 1972 June (Box-folder 169: 66)
      - Press releases
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 169: 67)
        - 1972 May-June (Box-folder 169: 68-69)
      - Remarks
        - 1970
          - May (Box-folder 169: 70)
          - November (Box-folder 169: 71)
        - 1972 May-June (Box-folder 169: 72-73)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 169: 74)
      - Schedules
        - 1970 November (Box-folder 169: 75)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 169: 76)
      - Statements, 1973 May (Box-folder 169: 77)
      - Telegrams, 1975 February (Box-folder 169: 78)
    - Middle East
      - Bulletins (Box-folder 170: 1)
      - Correspondence
        - 1973 October-November (Box-folder 170: 2-3)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 170: 4)
      - Executive orders, 1972 September (Box-folder 170: 5)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 170: 6)
        - General, 1973 (Box-folder 170: 7)
      - Interviews
        - 1973
          - February (Box-folder 170: 8)
          - April-May (Box-folder 170: 9-10)
        - 1974 November (Box-folder 170: 11)
        - 1975 January-February (Box-folder 170: 12-13)
      - Maps (Box-folder 170: 14)
      - Meetings
        - 1970 November (Box-folder 170: 15)
        - 1972 June (Box-folder 170: 16)
        - 1973
          - February-March (Box-folder 170: 17-18)
          - October-November (Box-folder 170: 19-20)
        - 1974 February-April (Box-folder 170: 21-23)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 170: 24)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 170: 25)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 170: 26)
        - 1973
          - January-February (Box-folder 170: 27-28)
          - October (Box-folder 170: 29)
        - 1974
          - August (Box-folder 170: 30)
          - October (Box-folder 170: 31)
      - Messages, 1970 January (Box-folder 170: 32)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1974 June (Box-folder 170: 33)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 170: 34)
      - Newsletters, 1973 February (Box-folder 170: 35)
      - News summaries
        - Undated (Box-folder 170: 36)
        - 1975 March (Box-folder 170: 37)
      - Pool reports
        - 1973
          - February (Box-folder 170: 38)
          - October (Box-folder 170: 39)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 170: 40)
          - August (Box-folder 170: 41)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 170: 42)
        - 1969 October (Box-folder 170: 43)
        - 1970 January (Box-folder 170: 44)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 170: 45)
        - 1973
          - February-March (Box-folder 170: 46-47)
          - October (Box-folder 170: 48)
        - 1974
          - February-April (Box-folder 170: 49-51)
          - June-July (Box-folder 170: 52-53)
        - 1975 May-July (Box-folder 170: 54-56)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 170: 57)
        - 1969
          - January (Box-folder 170: 58)
          - March (Box-folder 170: 59)
          - June (Box-folder 170: 60)
        - 1970
          - January (Box-folder 170: 61)
          - March (Box-folder 170: 62)
          - May (Box-folder 170: 63)
          - July (Box-folder 170: 64)
          - September (Box-folder 170: 65)
        - 1971 December (Box-folder 170: 66)
        - 1973
          - March (Box-folder 170: 67)
          - October (Box-folder 170: 68)
        - 1974 July (Box-folder 170: 69)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 170: 70)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 171: 1)
        - 1972 April (Box-folder 171: 2)
        - 1973 October-December (Box-folder 171: 3-5)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 171: 6)
          - March (Box-folder 171: 7)
          - May (Box-folder 171: 8)
        - 1975 March (Box-folder 171: 9)
      - Remarks
        - 1970 July (Box-folder 171: 10)
        - 1971 May (Box-folder 171: 11)
        - 1972
          - March (Box-folder 171: 12)
          - July (Box-folder 171: 13)
        - 1973
          - February-March (Box-folder 171: 14-15)
          - July (Box-folder 171: 16)
          - October (Box-folder 171: 17)
        - 1974
          - January-February (Box-folder 171: 18-19)
          - April-June (Box-folder 171: 20-22)
        - 1975 April-May (Box-folder 171: 23-24)
      - Schedules
        - General (Box-folder 171: 25)
        - 1974 March-April (Box-folder 171: 26-27)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 171: 28)
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 171: 29)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 171: 30)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 171: 31)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 171: 32)
          - May (Box-folder 171: 33)
          - July (Box-folder 171: 34)
        - 1975 March (Box-folder 171: 35)
      - Telegrams
        - 1970 February (Box-folder 171: 36)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 171: 37)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 171: 38)
      - Television news reports
        - 1971 November (Box-folder 171: 39)
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 171: 40)
        - 1973
          - January-February (Box-folder 171: 41-42)
          - September-December (Box-folder 171: 43-46)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 171: 47)
          - March-June (Box-folder 171: 48-51)
    - Morocco, remarks, 1970 January (Box-folder 171: 52)
    - Mozambique, press briefings, 1975 June (Box-folder 171: 53)
    - Netherlands
      - Correspondence, 1973 January (Box-folder 171: 54)
      - Memoranda, 1973 November (Box-folder 171: 55)
      - Remarks, 1975 May (Box-folder 171: 56)
    - New Zealand
      - Meetings, 1973 September (Box-folder 171: 57)
      - Press releases, 1970 June (Box-folder 171: 58)
      - Remarks, 1973 September (Box-folder 171: 59)
    - Nicaragua
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 171: 60)
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 171: 61)
      - Meetings, 1973 January (Box-folder 171: 62)
      - Memoranda
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 171: 63)
        - 1973 January (Box-folder 171: 64)
      - Press briefings, 1972 December (Box-folder 171: 65)
      - Press conferences
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 171: 66)
        - 1973 January (Box-folder 171: 67)
      - Press releases, 1972 December (Box-folder 171: 68)
      - Remarks, 1972 December (Box-folder 171: 69)
      - Schedules, 1973 January (Box-folder 171: 70)
    - Nigeria
      - Fact sheets, undated (Box-folder 171: 71)
      - Press briefings, 1970 January (Box-folder 171: 72)
      - Press conferences, 1970 January (Box-folder 171: 73)
      - Telegrams, 1970 January (Box-folder 171: 74)
    - Pakistan
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 171: 75)
        - 1971-1972 (Box-folder 171: 76)
      - Memoranda
        - 1971 September (Box-folder 171: 77)
        - 1973
          - June (Box-folder 171: 78)
          - September (Box-folder 171: 79)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 171: 80)
      - News summaries, undated (Box-folder 171: 81)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 172: 1)
        - 1971 August (Box-folder 172: 2)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 172: 3)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 172: 4)
      - Press conferences, 1970 November (Box-folder 172: 5)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 172: 6)
        - 1970 November (Box-folder 172: 7)
        - 1971 August (Box-folder 172: 8)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 172: 9)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 172: 10)
        - 1970 November (Box-folder 172: 11)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 172: 12)
      - Schedules, 1973 September (Box-folder 172: 13)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 172: 14)
        - 1971 January (Box-folder 172: 15)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 172: 16)
        - 1975 February (Box-folder 172: 17)
      - Telegrams, 1973 August (Box-folder 172: 18)
    - Panama
      - Press briefings, 1969 October (Box-folder 172: 19)
      - Press releases (printed copy), 1975 December (Box-folder 172: 20)
    - Paraguay, remarks, 1974 April (Box-folder 172: 21)
    - Peru
      - Fact sheets, 1974 February (Box-folder 172: 22)
      - Press conferences, 1970
        - June-July (Box-folder 172: 23-24)
        - September (Box-folder 172: 25)
      - Press releases, 1970
        - June (Box-folder 172: 26)
        - October (Box-folder 172: 27)
      - Remarks, 1970 June (Box-folder 172: 28)
      - Statements
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 172: 29)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 172: 30)
    - Philippines, executive orders, 1974 January (Box-folder 172: 31)
    - Portugal, press briefings, 1975 April (Box-folder 172: 32)
    - Prisoners of war and Americans missing in action
      - Correspondence
        - 1970
          - August (Box-folder 172: 33)
          - December (Box-folder 172: 34)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 172: 35)
          - June (Box-folder 172: 36)
          - December (Box-folder 172: 37)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 172: 38)
          - March (Box-folder 172: 39)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 172: 40)
          - March (Box-folder 172: 41)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 172: 42)
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 172: 43)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 172: 44)
          - December (Box-folder 172: 45)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 172: 46)
        - 1975 January (Box-folder 172: 47)
      - Interviews, 1971 August (Box-folder 172: 48)
      - Meetings
        - 1971 October (Box-folder 172: 49)
        - 1972 April-May (Box-folder 172: 50-51)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 172: 52)
          - March (Box-folder 172: 53)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 172: 54)
        - 1971 June (Box-folder 172: 55)
        - 1972 March-April (Box-folder 172: 56-57)
        - 1973 January-May (Box-folder 172: 58-62)
          Telephone memoranda.
      - Newsletters, 1973 February (Box-folder 172: 63)
      - News summaries
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 172: 64)
        - 1973 February (Box-folder 172: 65)
      - Pool reports, 1973 January (Box-folder 172: 66)
      - Press briefings
        - 1970 July (Box-folder 172: 67)
        - 1973 March-April (Box-folder 172: 68-69)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 172: 70)
      - Press conferences
        - 1972
          - May (Box-folder 172: 71)
          - September (Box-folder 172: 72)
        - 1973 February-March (Box-folder 172: 73-74)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 173: 1)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 173: 2)
      - Proclamations
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 173: 3)
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 173: 4)
        - 1972 March (Box-folder 173: 5)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 173: 6)
      - Remarks
        - 1972 September-October (Box-folder 173: 7-8)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 173: 9)
          - May (Box-folder 173: 10)
        - 1975 July (Box-folder 173: 11)
      - Schedules
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 173: 12)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 173: 13)
          - May (Box-folder 173: 14)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 173: 15)
        - 1970 August (Box-folder 173: 16)
        - 1971
          - April (Box-folder 173: 17)
          - June (Box-folder 173: 18)
        - 1973 February (Box-folder 173: 19)
      - Telegrams, 1973 February (Box-folder 173: 20)
    - Rhodesia
      - Memoranda, undated (Box-folder 173: 21)
      - Press briefings
        - 1970 February-March (Box-folder 173: 22-23)
          Includes statement.
        - 1971 November (Box-folder 173: 24)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 173: 25)
      - Telegrams, 1970 March (Box-folder 173: 26)
    - Romania
      - Communiques, 1973 December (Box-folder 173: 27)
      - Fact sheets, undated (Box-folder 173: 28)
      - Meetings, undated (Box-folder 173: 29)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 173: 30)
      - Press briefings
        - 1971 November (Box-folder 173: 31)
        - 1975 April (Box-folder 173: 32)
      - Press releases
        - 1971 November (Box-folder 173: 33)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 173: 34)
      - Remarks
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 173: 35)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 173: 36)
        - 1974 December (Box-folder 173: 37)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 173: 38)
      - Schedules
        - 1970 October (Box-folder 173: 39)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 173: 40)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 173: 41)
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 173: 42)
    - Singapore, remarks, 1975 May (Box-folder 173: 43)
    - South Asia
      - Correspondence, 1972 October (Box-folder 173: 44)
      - Press briefings, undated (Box-folder 173: 45)
      - Press conferences, 1971 December (Box-folder 173: 46)
      - Printed matter, 1972 January (Box-folder 173: 47)
      - Statements, 1971 December (Box-folder 173: 48)
      - Television news reports, 1971 November-December (Box-folder 173: 49-50)
    - Southeast Asia
      - Correspondence
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 173: 51)
        - 1972 July (Box-folder 173: 52)
      - Fact sheets, undated (Box-folder 173: 53)
      - Interviews, 1972 January (Box-folder 173: 54)
      - Maps (Box-folder 173: 55)
      - Meetings, 1970 May (Box-folder 173: 56)
      - Memoranda, 1973 January (Box-folder 173: 57)
      - Newsletters
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 173: 58)
        - 1972
          - April (Box-folder 173: 59)
          - November (Box-folder 173: 60)
      - News summaries, 1971 April (Box-folder 173: 61)
      - Press briefings
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 173: 62)
        - 1973 March (Box-folder 173: 63)
        - 1975 March-April (Box-folder 173: 64-65)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 173: 66)
        - 1970
          - March (Box-folder 173: 67)
          - June-July (Box-folder 173: 68-69)
        - 1971
          - January (Box-folder 173: 70)
          - March (Box-folder 173: 71)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 174: 1)
          - May (Box-folder 174: 2)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 174: 3)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 174: 4)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 174: 5)
        - 1975 April (Box-folder 174: 6)
      - Remarks
        - 1970
          - April (Box-folder 174: 7)
          - October (Box-folder 174: 8)
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 174: 9)
        - 1972 May (Box-folder 174: 10)
        - 1975 January-February (Box-folder 174: 11-12)
      - Reports
        - 1970 June (Box-folder 174: 13)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 174: 14)
      - Schedules
        - 1971 April (Box-folder 174: 15)
        - 1972 May (Box-folder 174: 16)
      - Statements
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 174: 17)
        - 1971 February (Box-folder 174: 18)
        - 1975 March (Box-folder 174: 19)
      - Telegrams
        - Undated (Box-folder 174: 20)
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 174: 21)
      - Television news reports
        - 1970 May (Box-folder 174: 22)
        - 1973 April (Box-folder 174: 23)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 174: 24)
      - Wire releases, 1971 May (Box-folder 174: 25)
    - Soviet Union
      - Communiques, 1974 February-March (Box-folder 174: 26-27)
      - Correspondence
        - 1970
          - April (Box-folder 174: 28)
          - August (Box-folder 174: 29)
          - November (Box-folder 174: 30)
        - 1972
          - February (Box-folder 174: 31)
          - June (Box-folder 174: 32)
          - October-November (Box-folder 174: 33-34)
        - 1973 April (Box-folder 174: 35)
      - Court proceedings, 1970 October (Box-folder 174: 36)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 174: 37)
        - 1971 May (Box-folder 174: 38)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 174: 39)
          - August-October (Box-folder 174: 40-42)
        - 1973 June (Box-folder 174: 43)
          Partly in Russian.
        - 1975 July (Box-folder 174: 44)
      - Meetings
        - 1971 October (Box-folder 174: 45)
        - 1972 October (Box-folder 174: 46)
        - 1973
          - April (Box-folder 174: 47)
          - June (Box-folder 174: 48)
          - September (Box-folder 174: 49)
        - 1974
          - April-May (Box-folder 174: 50-51)
          - September (Box-folder 174: 52)
      - Memoranda
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 174: 53)
          - August-October (Box-folder 174: 54-56)
        - 1973
          - February-March (Box-folder 174: 57-58)
          - June (Box-folder 174: 59)
          - August (Box-folder 174: 60)
          - September (Box-folder 175: 1)
          - November (Box-folder 175: 2)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 175: 3)
          - June (Box-folder 175: 4)
          - December (Box-folder 175: 5)
      - Messages
        - 1969 November (Box-folder 175: 6)
        - 1974 October (Box-folder 175: 7)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 175: 8)
      - Newsletters
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 175: 9)
        - 1972
          - May (Box-folder 175: 10)
          - August-September (Box-folder 175: 11-12)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 175: 13)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 175: 14)
        - 1975
          - May-June (Box-folder 175: 15)
          - June-July (Box-folder 175: 16-17)
      - News summaries
        - Undated (Box-folder 175: 18)
        - 1971 May (Box-folder 175: 19)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 175: 20)
          - September-November (Box-folder 175: 21-23)
        - 1973 February (Box-folder 175: 24)
        - 1975 July (Box-folder 175: 25)
      - Pool reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 175: 26)